<resources>
    <string name="app_name"></string>
    <string name="mchat_intro">Please answer these questions about your child. Keep in mind how your child usually behaves. If you have seen your child do the behavior a few times, but he or she does not usually do it, then please answer no. Please choose yes or no for every question. Thank you very much.</string>
    <string name="mchat_info">*The Modified Checklist for Autism in Toddlers-Revised (M-CHAT-R™) is a scientifically validated tool for screening children between 16 and 30 months of age that assesses risk for autism spectrum disorder (ASD).</string>
    <string name="question1">If you point at something across the room, does your child look at it?</string>


    <!-- Score screen strings -->

    <string name="low_risk">A score of 2 indicates Low-Risk</string>

    <string name="low_risk_description">If child is younger than 24 months, screen again after
        second birthday. No further action required unless surveillance indicates risk for ASD.</string>

    <string name="medium_risk">A score of 3 indicates Low-Risk</string>

    <string name="medium_risk_description">Administer the Follow-up (second stage of M-CHAT-R/F) to
        get additional information about at-risk responses. If M-CHAT-R/F score remains at 2 or higher,
        the child has screened positive. Action required: refer child for diagnostic evaluation and
        eligibility evaluation for early intervention. If score on Follow-up is 0-1, child has screened
        negative. No further action required unless surveillance indicates risk for ASD. Child should
        be re-screened at future well-child visits.</string>

    <string name="high_risk_description">It is acceptable to bypass the Follow-up and refer immediately
        for diagnostic evaluation and eligibility evaluation for early intervention.</string>

    <string name="mchat_description">The M-CHAT-R can be administered and scored as part of a well-child
        care visit, and also can be used by specialists or other professionals to assess risk for ASD.
        The primary goal of the M-CHAT-R is to maximize sensitivity, meaning to detect as many cases
        of ASD as possible. Therefore, there is a high false positive rate, meaning that not all children
        who score at risk will be diagnosed with ASD. Users should be aware that although a significant
        number of children who screen positive on the M-CHAT-R will not be diagnosed with ASD, these
        children are at high risk for other developmental disorders or delays, and therefore, evaluation
        is warranted for any child who screens positive.</string>

    <string name = "autism_info">Autism spectrum disorder (ASD) is a complex developmental disability,
        typically appearing during childhood and affecting a person\'\s ability to communicate and interact with others.</string>
    <string name="autism_diagram_description">As illustrated by the graph above, the basic symptoms of autism are often accompanied by other medical conditions and challenges. These, too, can vary widely in severity.</string>
    <string name="autism_society_description">The Autism Society of America has been improving the lives of all affected by autism for over 50 years and envisions a world where individuals and families living with autism are able to maximize their quality of life, are treated with the highest level of dignity, and live in a society in which their talents and skills are appreciated and valued. We provide advocacy, education, information and referral, support, and community at national, state and local levels through our strong nationwide network of Affiliates.</string>

    <string-array name="Questions">
        <item name="question1">If you point at something across the room, does your child look at it?</item>
        <item name="question2">Have you ever wondered if your child might be deaf?</item>
        <item name="question3">Does your child play pretend or make-believe?</item>
        <item name="question4">Does your child like climbing on things?</item>
        <item name="question5">Does your child make unusual finger movements near his or her eyes?</item>
        <item name="question6">Does your child point with one finger to ask for something or to get help?</item>
        <item name="question7">Does your child point with one finger to show you something interesting?</item>
        <item name="question8">Is your child interested in other children?</item>
        <item name="question9">Does your child show you things by bringing them to you or holding them up for you to see - not to get help, but just to share?</item>
        <item name="question10">Does your child respond when you call his or her name?</item>
        <item name="question11">When you smile at your child, does he or she smile back at you?</item>
        <item name="question12">Does your child get upset by everyday noises?</item>
        <item name="question13">Does your child walk?</item>
        <item name="question14">Does your child look you in the eye when you are talking to him or her, playing with him or her, or dressing him or her? </item>
        <item name="question15">Does your child try to copy what you do?</item>
        <item name="question16">If you turn your head to look at something, does your child look around to see what you are looking at?</item>
        <item name="question17">Does your child try to get you to watch him or her?</item>
        <item name="question18">Does your child understand when you tell him or her to do something?</item>
        <item name="question19">If something new happens, does your child look at your face to see how you feel about it?</item>
        <item name="question20">Does your child like movement activities?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Examples">
        <item name="example1">If you point at a toy or an animal, does your child look at the toy or animal?</item>
        <item name="example2">No example</item>
        <item name="example3">Pretend to drink from an empty cup, pretend to talk on a phone, or pretend to feed a doll or stuffed animal?</item>
        <item name="example4">Furniture, playground equipment, or stairs.</item>
        <item name="example5">Does your child wiggle his or her fingers close to his or her eyes?</item>
        <item name="example6">Pointing to a snack or toy that is out of reach.</item>
        <item name="example7">Pointing to an airplane in the sky or a big truck in the road.</item>
        <item name="example8">Does your child watch other children, smile at them, or go to them?</item>
        <item name="example9">Showing you a flower, a stuffed animal, or a toy truck.</item>
        <item name="example10">Does he or she look up, talk or babble, or stop what he or she is doing when you call his or her name?</item>
        <item name="example11">No example</item>
        <item name="example12">Does your child scream or cry to noise such as a vacuum cleaner or loud music?</item>
        <item name="example13">No example</item>
        <item name="example14">No example</item>
        <item name="example15">Wave bye-bye, clap, or make a funny noise when you do.</item>
        <item name="example16">No example</item>
        <item name="example17">Does your child look at you for praise, or say “look” or “watch me”?</item>
        <item name="example18">If you don’t point, can your child understand “put the book on the chair” or “bring me the blanket”?</item>
        <item name="example19">If he or she hears a strange or funny noise, or sees a new toy, will he or she look at your face?.</item>
        <item name="example20">Being swung or bounced on your knee</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
